<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="image_selection_storage_option">"Gallery"</string>
    <string name="image_selection_storage_help">When the gallery button is pressed. It will allow you to select an image stored within your device.</string>

    <string name="image_selection_camera_option">Camera</string>
    <string name="image_selection_camera_help">When the camera button is pressed. It will shows you
        the camera view from which you can take a picture.</string>

    <string name="image_selection_internet_option">Internet</string>
    <string name="image_selection_internet_help">To get an image from the internet. \nStep 1 copy
        the URL (i.e. www.google.com) of the image. \nStep 2 past it into the search box. \nStep 3
        press the search button. \nIf it does not work double check that the URL is correct, and
        that the device is connected to the internet.</string>

    <string name="image_selection_sample_option">Sample</string>
    <string name="image_selection_sample_help">You should see a row of images. Swipe through to find an image that you like and press it.</string>

    <string name="image_selection_history_option">History</string>
    <string name="image_selection_history_help">You should see a row of images. Swipe
        through to find an image that you like and press it. All these images are images
        that you have traced in your past.</string>


    <string name="image_tracing_reset_option">Reset</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_reset_help">When the reset button is pressed. It will undo all
        changes made to the image.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_resize_option">Resize</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_resize_help">When the resize, switch is pressed. It will enable or disable the gestures for rotation, resizing and movement. If the switch is on these gestures are enabled. If the switch is off the image is locked in place.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_flip_option">Flip</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_flip_help">
        When one of the flip options is pressed the image is flipped on that axis.
        \nThe x axis option will make everything on the left swap with everything on the right.
        \nThe y axis option will make everything on the top swap with everything on the bottom.
        \nThe both option applies both the x axis and the y axis to the image.
        \nThis is useful when positioning the image.
    </string>

    <string name="image_tracing_edge_detection_option">Edge detection</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_edge_detection_help">
        Edge detection will find edges of objects in the image.
        \nThe Low option will find only the most prominent edges.
        \nThe High option will most of the edges in the image.
        \nThis is useful for focusing on the edges when drawing.
    </string>

    <string name="image_tracing_image_segmentation_option">Split image</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_image_segmentation_help">Split image will cut out objects from the
        background. Hiding the background and leaving the objects.
        This is useful for focusing on the objects within an image.
    </string>

    <string name="image_tracing_invert_option">Invert</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_invert_help">When the invert colour button is pressed. It will switch the colours in the image to their opposite. For example, white becomes black. This would help make it easier to identify different colours.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_colour_option">Colour</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_colour_help">When one of the colour bars is moved. Some of the
        colours will be removed. For example, if all bars are at 0 then all colours apart from black will be removed. This would help by allowing you to draw the image one colour at a time.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_colour_merge_option">Colour merge</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_colour_merge_help">Colour merge will blend the colours of the image
        together. This simplifies the image into its most prominent colours.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_blur_option">Blur</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_blur_help">Blur this will blur the image. This is useful to hide
        complex parts of the image and highlight prominent parts of the image.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_colour_overlay_option">Colour Overlay</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_colour_overlay_help">Colour overlay will colour the entire image in
        the selected option. If two colours are hard to tell apart from each other having an
        overlay might help.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_transparency_option">Transparency</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_transparency_help">When the transparency bar is moved. The image will fade into the background. If the bar is at 100 then the image will be completely visible, at 0 then the image will be invisible. This would help when tracing with the camera as you will be able to see what you are drawing through the image.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_contrast_option">Contrast</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_contrast_help">When the contrast bar is moved. This will make the colours on image more distinguishable. When the brightness bar is moved. This will increase or decrease the brightness of the image.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_shadow_option">Shadows</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_shadow_help">When the shadows bar is moved. This will highlight the darkness parts of the image. This would allow you focus on the shadows in the image.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_monochrome_option">Monochrome</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_monochrome_help">When the monochrome button is pressed. All colour from the image is removed and replace with either black or white. This would help to make the image easier to view.</string>

    <string name="image_tracing_black_and_white_option">Black and white</string>
    <string name="image_tracing_black_and_white_help">Black and white will replace all colours in
        the selected image with either black or white. This is useful for focusing on the shapes
        that make up the image instead of the colours in the image.</string>

</resources>